20, 20 more.
Have the education by pastor?
May I release?
Other blessed these people in front of us,
bless them in those hard moments when they're
people being goofy on a screen,
continue to give them confidence and what they're doing
those tough times and let them know that we do appreciate them.
Father, I thank you for the way you notice our town
and you don't just see up on the road, but you see people here like we do.
Thank you for caring about us and I pray that we will continue to lean on you
and let you help us.
Father, tonight as we meet, give us wisdom, give them wisdom more.
Jesus name, I pray, amen.
Amen.
I'd like to believe in the Institute of the Black,
the United States, America, and the Institute of the Republic
for which it stands, one on the nation, and one on your body,
anything that is worth the liberty of justice to our honor.
How are you?
Before we go again, but unscheduled personal experiences,
five volumes list, most of you approve.
Thank you.
Are you deaf?
I don't want to.
Hi.
I'm a deaf person.
Thank you.
Six minutes from the January 2nd.
Twenty-four rigor and meeting, most of you approve.
Second.
Is that?
Five.
So, you'd all strapped in Edmunds, a bomber claim, for Gerardier,
a relaxing amount of $210.
So, Mayor, remember to the council?
This claim is for services that occurred at the World Court of November 24th,
due to summer 15th, which is a fairly narrow time span there,
hence the small amount, but we did have some meetings
that have happened during that time, or we discussed,
dam safety issues, relicent, zig-state plan,
contaminated, sediment, study, transport study, and the in-half amendment,
and sort of a court of appeals follow-up.
Therefore, I'm asking approval of this claim.
This would go against our annually budget at 750,000.
The current balance is $557,042.
So, I'm just asking for you to approve this $210 claim at this time.
Thank you.
Five.
Eight.
Any business?
Supposing this agenda?
Nine.
Staff reports.
Can't trust the community in Africa 11 this meeting will be continued from California to be in the staff room
The purpose of the executive session the completion of the regular schedule meeting is my city council